Guide to the Office of the Dean, Washington Square College and Washington Square and University College of Arts and Science 1929-1984 (Bulk 1951-1980) RG.19
New York University Archives
- Series I: Washington Square Dean's Files
  - Subseries C: Educational Policy Committee
    - Educational Policy Committee: General, 1965-1966 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Educational Policy Committee: General, 1970-1971 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Educational Policy Committee: General, 1971-1972 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Achievement Tests, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Actions Completed (Hindle), 1966-1967 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Admissions Standards, 1958-1964 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04225990 6
    - Educational Policy Committee: Advanced Standing, 1958-1963 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Educational Policy Committee: American Civilization Concentration, 1968 December 12 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Announcements, Minutes, Reports, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Annual Report to the Dean, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Anthropology (Hindle), 1966 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Black Studies, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Brazil Junior Year Program, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Class Attendance, 1958-1968 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Class Scheduling, 1963-1965 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Class Size, 1957-1964 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Completed Business (Minor), 1966 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Coordinated Liberal Studies, Commission on, 1969-1978 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Correspondence, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Correspondence and Minutes, 1964-1965 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Courses Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Courses to be Approved, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Creative Arts, 1966-1967 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Curricular Innovation Fund, 1968-1969 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Curriculum Committee, Undergraduate, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Debating, 1961-1962 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Departmental Planning, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Discipline Procedures, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Dramatic Literature Major, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Educational Policy Committee: East Asian Studies, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Electives, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Educational Policy Committee: English Courses, 1960-1968 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Educational Policy Committee: English Major, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Educational Policy Committee: English 1roficiency, 1959-1966 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Evening Program, 1959-1964 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Examinations, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Examinations, Program of Coordinated Liberal Studies, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04225991 4
    - Educational Policy Committee: F Grade Substitution, 1962-1964 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Faculty Role, Definition of, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Foreign Language Requirements, 1953-1967 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Foreign Students, 1960-1965 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Four-Course Plan, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Four-Course Plan, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Freshman Orientation, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Gallatin Divison, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Geology, 1951-1962 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Geophysics, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Germany Study Program, 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Grading (Pass-Fail and Plus-Minus), 1964-1969 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Grading System, 1957-1968 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Graduate Courses, 1957-1968 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Graduate Record Exam, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Graduate Study in Psychology, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Graduate Survey, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Hanging Business (Minor), 1965-1966 (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Hebrew, 1959-1965 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Honors, 1959-1966 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Hours, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Independent Study, 1957-1960 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Israel Summer Session, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Linguistics Major, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Major Selection, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Mandate, 1951-1965 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Mathematics Major, 1958-1965 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Membership, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Metropolitan Leadership Program Evaluation, 1968 November 1 (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Mid-Term Grades, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Minor Requirements, 1957-1963 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Minutes, 1967-1968 (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Minutes, 1968-1969 (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 54, Folder 30)
    - Educational Policy Committee: N Grade, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Educational Policy Committee: New General Program, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Non-Liberal Arts Credit, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Philosophy, 1958-1961 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Physical Education, 1962-1965 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Physical Science, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04225992 2
    - Educational Policy Committee: Planning, 1968-1969 (Box 54, Folder 31)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Portuguese-Brazilian major, 1958-1965 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Proficiency Examination, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Educational Policy Committee: R Course Requirement, 1961-1962 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Reading Period, 1966-1968 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Reading Week, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 32)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Recommendations on Faculty Involvement (Hindle), circa 1960s-1970s (Box 54, Folder 33)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Recommendations, Program of Coordinated Liberal Studies, 1957-1965 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Religion, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Report to the Faculty, 1968-1969 (Box 54, Folder 34)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Report on Graduate Study in the Arts and Sciences at University Heights, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 35)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Reserve Officers Training Program, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Reserve Officers Training Corps (ROTC) Proposals, 1968-1969 (Box 54, Folder 36)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Russian Area Studies, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Scholastic Standing Committee, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 37)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Scholastic Standing Reform, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 38)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Science Requirement, 1961-1966 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Social Science Integration, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Spain, New York University in, 1960-1966 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Speech, 1962-1965 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Educational Policy Committee: State Proficiency Exams, 1957-1969 (Box 54, Folder 39)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Statistics Major, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Student Participation, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 40)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Student Petition on Tenure, 1969 March (Box 54, Folder 41)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Superior Student Privileges, 1962-1963 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Terminations, Program of Coordinated Liberal Studies, 1963-1966 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Educational Polciy Committee: Testing: Advanced, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Three Year M.A., 1960-1964 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Television, Motion Pictures and Radio, Department of, 1963-1965 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Tutorial Group, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Educational Policy Committee: University Scholars, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Upperclass Programs, 1957-1961 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Educational Policy Committee: World Literature Minor, 1968 October-November (Box 54, Folder 42)
  - Subseries D: Administrative Subject Files
    - Afro-American Course Offerings, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04225993 0
    - Alumni Association Seminars, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Alumni News, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Alumni Relations, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - American Council on Education, 1962-1968 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Applications to New York University, 1973-1979 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Applied Economics, Center for, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Applied Mathematics Proposal, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Archaeological Institute of America: Color Film on Greece, 1953-1956 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Archaelogical Institute of America: Committee on Films and Television, 1954-1971 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Archaeological Institute of America: Greek Temple Film, 1958-1959 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Archaeological Institute of America: Visual Arts Committee, 1955-1971 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Articulation Programs, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Big Apple Volunteer Fair, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Chairmanships, Departmental, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - City University of New York, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Commencement: 1970 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Commencement: 1971 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Commencement: 1972 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Commencement: 1973 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Commencement: 1974 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Comparative Literature, 1963-1974 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04225994 8
    - Comparative Literature: Undergraduate Major, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Confidential Task Force, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Continuing Education, School of, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Crisis Period: May 1970 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Crisis Period: May 1970: Cambodia (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Crisis Period: May 1970: Department Reports (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Curriculum Committee, Undergraduate, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Dean McKee, 1966-1971 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Deems Lecutre Committee, 1965-1968 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Degree Requirements, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Dr. W. Lewis Hyde, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Drama, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Empire State Program, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Environmental Problems, 1970-1973 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Faculty Appointments, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Faculty of Arts and Science, Minutes of the, 1974-1976 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Goals Conference, 1 of 6, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04225995 5
    - Goals Conference, 2 of 6, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Goals Conference, 3 of 6, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Goals Conference, 4 of 6, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Goals Conference, 5 of 6, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Goals Conference, 6 of 6, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Harout's Experiment, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Humanities Program, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Ibero-American Studies, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - India, Seminar in, 1966-1968 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Institutional Services, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04225996 3
    - Inter-American Institute of Ecology, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - International Affairs Center, 1963-1965 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - International Development Research Center, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - International Education, Institute of, 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - International Research and Exchange Board, 1970-1972 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - International Student Center (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - International Studies Center, 1965-1971 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - International Studies Center: Policy Council, 1956-1968 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Internships, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Inventions and Patents, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Irish Studies, 1964-1973 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Israel, Summer Session in, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - J File, 1964-1967 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Japanese Studies, 1965-1966 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Junior Years (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Library Strike, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Linguistics Program, 1968-1972 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Lobbying, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Lobbying, Higher Education, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Luce Scholars Program, 1973-1975 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Luso-Brazilian Studies, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - M File, 1963-1967 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Majors, Distribution at New York University, 1965-1975 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Management Development and Training, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - McGhee Concerts, 1955-1966 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - McKay Committee: Report, 1967-1974 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Medicine, School of, 1963-1973 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - M.D.-Ph.D., Joint Program at New York University, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Memoranda File, 1968-1973 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04225997 1
    - Memoranda Issued by Dean of the Faculty, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Mental Health Center, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Middle States Association, 1964-1973 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Mid-Term Grades, 1965-1968 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Minority Group Programs, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Model Programs, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Modern Language Association, 1964-1969 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - N File, 1963-1968 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People: The Committee of 100, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - National Association of Teacher's Agencies, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - National Broadcasting Company, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - National Defense Authorization, 1966-1970 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities: Applications, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities: Newsletters, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - National Institute of Education, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - National Institute of Health, 1962-1975 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - National Labor Relations Board, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - National League for Nursing, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - National Research Council, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - New York State Correspondence, 1967-1975 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - New York State Education Department: Awarding Credit for Same Course in Different Degree Programs, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - New York State Education Department: Foreign Area Materials Center, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - New York State Education Department: Programs, 1969-1975 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - New York Times, Challenge from the, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - New York University Press, 1965-1976 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - New York University Press Policy Council, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Nobel Peace Prize, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Non-Credit Courses, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Non-Graded Courses, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Placement Services, 1963-1975 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Popular Courses, 1974-1977 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Priorities in Higher Education Task Force, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04225998 9
    - Promotions Pending, 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Promotions, Recommendations for, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Recruitment, Admissions, and Scholarship, Commission on, 1965-1967 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Sabbatical Leaves, Applications for, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Security Incident Reports, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Senate Elected Areas (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Soviet Union, a Guide to Study in the, 1959-1960 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Spain, American Academy in, 1963-1967 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Square Journal Clippings, 1959-1965 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Student Conduct Memos, 1968-1970 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Student Participation (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Student Union, the New, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Washington Square College Fiftieth Anniversary: Dinner, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Washington Square College Fiftieth Anniversary: General File, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Washington Square College Fiftieth Anniversary: Lecture, undated (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Washington Square and University College Council, 1973-1976 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Financial: Alcoa Foundation, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04225999 7
    - Financial: Ann Petluck Poses Scholarship Fund, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Financial: Benjamin Salom Memorial Award for Biological Research, 1972-1974 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Financial: Biology and Psychology, Fund Raising for, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Financial: Budget Meetings, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Financial: Carnegie Corporation, 1974-1977 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Financial: Classics Department, Discretionary Fund of the, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Financial: Clubs, Budgets for, 1977-1978 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Financial: Danforth Foundation, 1971-1972 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Financial: Delmore Schwartz Memorial Poetry Fund, 1966-1974 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Financial: Development: Campaign Meeting, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Financial: Development: General File, 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Financial: Development: General File, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Financial: Development: General File, 1971-1972 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Financial: Development: General File, 1972-1974 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Financial: Development, Office for, 1963-1978 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Financial: Development, Office for: Arts and Sciences, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Financial: Edward H. Innet, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Financial: Effective Use of Resources, Commission on the, 1968-1970 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Financial: Esso Education Foundation, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Financial: Foundation Giving, 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Financial: Foundation Summaries, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Financial: Gottesman Foundation, 1971-1977 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Financial: Graduate Record Exam, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04226000 3
    - Financial: Housing, Departmental Budget for, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Financial: Post Seconddary Research Fund, 1975-1976 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Financial: Japanese Studies at NYU, Fund Raising for, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Financial: Jean R. Fitzhugh, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Financial: Louis Calder Foundation, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Financial: Mabel Rabkin Fund Raising Steering Committee, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Financial: Mail Complaints, 1968-1973 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      bar code #: 3 1142 042260003
    - Financial: Maitland Lecture, 1959-1967 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Financial: Mellon Foundation Professorships, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Financial: Morgan Guaranty Trust, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Financial: Nader, Ralph, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Financial: NEH, 1966-1975 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Financial: NEH: Faculty Grants, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Financial: NEH: Visual Arts Program, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Financial: Netzer Committee Fiscal Review, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Financial: Oliva Commission, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Financial: Pre-Med Fellowships, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 18)
      bar code #:3 1142 04226000 3
    - Financial: Receptions, Departmental Funding for, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Financial: Ryan, Marjorie Langley: Estate of, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Financial: School Revenues, Expenses, and Capital Expenditures, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Financial: Security Officer Contracts, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Financial: Stewart Mott Scholarship for Political Leadership, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Financial: Student Center Reservations, 1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Financial: Student Lounges, 1964-1974 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Sunrise Semester: Correspondence File, 1971-1977 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04226001 1
    - Sunrise Semester: Educational Policy Committee, 1958-1977 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Sunrise Semester: Examinations, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Sunrise Semseter: Fan Mail, 1971-1977 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Sunrise Semester: Fund Raising, 1971-1977 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Sunrise Semester: Hearst Foundation, 1972-1977 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Sunrise Semester: National Endowment for the Humanities, 1973-1975 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Sunrise Semester: Proposals, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Sunrise Semester: Publicity, 1972-1977 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Advisement, 1963-1974 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04226002 9
    - Advisement: Background for Reference, 1961-1962 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Advisement: Student Correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Advisory Committee Subcommittees, 1943-1975 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Advisory Council on Continuing Education, undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Affirmative Action, Office of, 1971-1973 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Affirmative Action, Office of, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Air Conditioning, 1959-1970 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Album, 1964-1967 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Alpha Fraternities, 1952-1966 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Alternate Education Program, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - American Academy of Dramatic Arts, 1958-1959 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - American Architectural Experience, 1975-1976 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - American Association of Higher Education, 1971-1973 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - American Committee for Émigré Scholars, 1960-1964 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - American Conference of Academic Deans, 1968-1975 (Box 26, Folder 16)